{
    "subject": "resource/South_Sudan",
    "predicate": "property/commonName",
    "object": "South Sudan",
    "human_readable": "The common name of South Sudan is South Sudan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9822196960449219,
            "question": "What is the common name of South Sudan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9347370862960815,
            "question": "Is 'South Sudan' the official name of the country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9007999897003174,
            "question": "Does South Sudan have any other commonly used names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6758061051368713,
            "question": "What region is South Sudan located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6069372296333313,
            "question": "Describe the geography of South Sudan."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5811933875083923,
            "question": "Who are some prominent leaders of South Sudan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5034403800964355,
            "question": "What is the official language of South Sudan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39075732231140137,
            "question": "What are some important cultural traditions in South Sudan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37543949484825134,
            "question": "What are some major challenges facing South Sudan today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2068551629781723,
            "question": "When did South Sudan become independent?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The common name of South Sudan is South Sudan.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8554_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some major challenges facing South Sudan today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8554_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some important cultural traditions in South Sudan?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8554_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the official language of South Sudan?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8554_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8554_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8554_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8554_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8554_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8554_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8554_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8554_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8554_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8554_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8554_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can provide the following response:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis answer indicates that the statement \"The common name of South Sudan is South Sudan\" is supported by the documents. In fact, the last document explicitly mentions \"South Sudan, a country located in northeast Africa...\" which confirms that the common name of this country is indeed \"South Sudan\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe query \"The common name of South Sudan is South Sudan\" aligns with the provided context which states, \"South Sudan, a country located in northeast Africa, is known for its ethnic and cultural diversity.\" This indicates that the common name used to refer to this country is indeed South Sudan."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}